Marlon R. Dela Cruz marlon.dcrodriguez@gmail.com +63 995 385 6860



Objective

I have worked as an IT Specialist for five years and was promoted to IT Supervisor, where I have been for the past four years. In total, I have gained nine years of experience in my current position. My goal is to continue exploring the IT industry and expanding my knowledge within it. I am seeking a secure position within a prestigious, fast-paced company that values teamwork and offers opportunities for professional development. I am eager to utilize my skills and years of experience to contribute to the success of the organization.

Education

2008-2010, Associate in Two Year Computer Science Asian Institute of Computer Studies (AICS) Marilao City, Bulacan

Work Experience

SAP Analyst

Unilever Philippines - Leadpack Foods Corporation 3PM (Aug 2012 - Jan 2013)

- Encoding Daily Production
- Checking the Product Inventory
- Solving COGI's of SAP System

IT-Supervisor

Everest Plastic Containers Industry, Inc. (Apr 2013 - 2022)

- System & Network Administrator
- Continues Project implementation for IT Infrastructure and company process development
- SAP Business 1 Administrator
- Onsite & Voice Support
- CMS Administrator for company websites
- Firewall Monitoring (FortiGate 101E)
- Maintaining CCTV Security
- Maintaining and Monitoring of IT Inventory
- NAS Admin
- CPANEL Admin
- Supervising & Monitoring IT Specialist and IT Staffs

Skills

- Teamwork
- Analytical thinking
- Operating systems (Windows & Linux)
- Microsoft Office
- Photoshop (Basic Editing)
- Video Editing
- Troubleshooting
- Database administration
- Excellent interpersonal skills
- Bitdefender Gravityzone
- CCTV Camera / NVR devices
- PABX Panasonic KX-NS300/NS320
- VLAN Switching
- Network Admin
- Biometric Devices

Languages

English, Tagalog

Hobbies and Interests

- Mountain Biking (Downhill / Enduro)
- FPS Games
- Art
- Vlog (youtube channel not monitized)

Certificates Received:

- ❖ Completion of the Oracle University Course: "Oracle Database 10g: Introduction to SQL"
- ❖ Completion of the Oracle University Course: "Oracle Database 9i: Database Administration Fundamentals I"
- ❖ CCNA4 WAN Technologies
- ❖ CCNA3 Switching Basics & Intermediate Routing
- ❖ CCNA2 Router & Routing Basics
- ❖ CCNA1 Networking Basics
- "JAVA Programming Course"
- ❖ UNIX Essentials Featuring Solaris 10 Operating System
- ❖ Safety and Proper Operation Seminar on NICHIYU™ Electric FORKLIFT(Conducted by: NICHIYU ASIALIFT PHILS., INC.)